

#### FULL STACK .NET DEVELOPE

Tehran, Iran

□ (+98)9120453091 | 🔀 kami.jami@gmail.com | 🔏 alirezajami.ir | 🖸 kami-jami | 🛅 alireza-jami



## **Summary**

Hardworking software engineer with 10+ years of experience, looking for the opportunity to follow a successful career in software development. Experience working for a diverse clientele with .NET and SQL skills. Designed and developed over 15 advanced applications from use cases and functional requirements. Experience in design and development of web-based applications using .NET Framework.

# Work Experience \_\_\_

#### Central Organization Of Azad University (IAU CO)

Tehran, Iran

Head Of Development Department Nov. 2017 - Present

- Effectively directed and oversaw staff. designing schedules to meet the needs of the department as well as the needs of employees.
- · Oversaw all aspects of design and development. and offered design solutions when necessary.

### **Central Organization Of Azad University (IAU CO)**

Tehran, Iran

SENIOR DEVELOPMENT SPECIALIST

May. 2015 - Nov. 2017

- Developed and presented findings and solutions to audiences including senior executives and stakeholders.
- Documented all concerns and incidents and reported them to a senior supervisor.
- Designing and building the university president's website
- Designing and building a portal for direct public communication with the university president
- Designing and building a survey portal and communicating with students
- Designing and building software under Windows for easy control of follow-up matters
- Designing and building web-based software for mechanizing dissertations

#### Rayaneh Gostar Doran Co. · Part-time

Borūjerd, Lorestan, Iran

Apr. 2012 - Apr. 2015

- Chairman of the Board
- Effectively directed and oversaw staff. designing schedules to meet the needs of the department as well as the needs of employees.
- Ensured the privacy and security of a customer's files every step of the way.
- Designing and installing the site network of the paramedical faculty of Borujerd branch

#### **Azad University Borujerd Branch**

Borūjerd, Lorestan, Iran

Oct. 2011 - Dec. 2014

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY ENGINEER

- Worked to constantly network with new clients and maintain relations with former clients.
- Maintained optimal network performance by performing network monitoring and analysis.
- Provided assistance to network users regarding troubleshooting and procedures.
- Worked to maintain the confidentiality of information and network data.
- Advised staff on effective utilization of existing network resources and tools.
- Assisted with the evaluation and selection of network hardware and software.
- Analyzed network components to identify beneficial improvements.
- Design and implementation of internal software required by the organization
- Serving the server room
- Installation of servers
- Set up a wireless network
- · Support for wireless and cable networks

#### Speed Processors Company.(BITC) · Part-time

Borūjerd, Lorestan, Iran

Sep. 2007 - Jun. 2011

JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

- Planned, developed, tested, deployed, and maintained web and windows applications.
- Designing and building the portal of Sama College, Borujerd branch
- Designing and building the job seekers portal of the Ministry of Cooperation
- Design and construction of virtual library

### Azad University Borujerd Branch · Internship

Borūjerd, Lorestan, Iran

Sep. 2006 - Feb. 2011

SERVICE DESK SPECIALIST

• Served as computer site operator.

OCTOBER 18, 2022 ALIREZA JAMI · RÉSUMÉ 1

### **Education**

#### **Azad University Borujerd Branch**

B.S. IN COMPUTER SOFTWARE ENGINEERING

#### **Azad University Borujerd Branch**

A.S. IN APPLIED SCIENCE OF COMPUTER SOFTWARE

Borujerd, Lorestan, Iran

Sep. 2008 - Mar. 2011

Jul. 2006 - Feb. 2009

Nov. 2018 - Apr. 2019

Jun. 2022 - Jul. 2022

Aug. 2018 - Sep. 2018

Jul. 2022 - Jul. 2022

Borujerd, Lorestan, Iran

### Languages

**English** Intermediate Persian Mother Tongue

### Skills

Web Architecture Approaches Microservice, Monolithic

programming languages C#, Python

> Back-end ASP.NET Core, Django, Express.js

Front-end HTML, CSS(Bootstrap, SASS), Javascript, TypeScript, Angular

Database and SQL MS SQL Server, Mongodb, Redis, PostgreSQL

API Architectural Rest API, gRPC

Version Control Github, TFS, Bitbucket, Gitlab ORMs Entity Framework, Dapper

> **DevOps** Docker, Kubernetes

**Web Technologies** RabbitMQ, Ocelot, AutoMapper, Elasticsearch, Kibana, Portainer

# **Extracurricular Activity**

**Microservices** Tehran, Iran

FREELANCE Jul. 2022 - Sep. 2022

• ASP.NET, Redis, Mongodb, PostgreSQL, RabbitMq, Docker, gRPC

• https://github.com/kami-jami/AspnetMicroservices

**Dating App** Tehran, Iran

· Asp.net & Angular

FREELANCE

**FREELANCE** 

FREELANCE

https://github.com/kami-jami/DatingApp

**Personal Tracking Project** Tehran, Iran

· C# Project • https://github.com/kami-jami/PersonalTracking

**Local Library** Tehran, Iran

· Django Project

• https://github.com/kami-jami/locallibrary

Project by RabbitMq Tehran, Iran

FREELANCE

RabbitMq Project

• https://github.com/kami-jami/RabbitMqProductAPI